汉克  谢谢你能来
Thanks for coming, Hank.
我知道你不喜欢这种场合
I know this isn't your style,
但我喜欢时不时拉你出来显摆
but I like to show you off from time to time.
我很乐意来
Listen, I'm glad to be here.
现在没几个政客
There's not too many politicians
愿意公开支持警察了
willing to publically support the police these days.
-我得去握手了  -去吧
- I got to go press the flesh. - Do it.
你怎么也被拉来了
How'd you get dragged into this?
我朋友  我男朋友邀请我来的
Uh, my friend-- my boyfriend invited me.
他几年前为格雷诺议员工作过
He worked with Congressman Graynor a few years back
就在地检办公室
at the State's Attorney's Office.
-你看起来很不错  -谢谢
- Well, you look great. - Thanks.
上次我穿这件衣服是在我阿姨的葬礼上
I mean, the last time I wore this was my aunt's funeral.
还有用武之地挺好的
Glad you're getting some use out of it.
谢谢
Thanks.
你的新男友在哪呢
So where is this new guy?
还没到  我也不清楚
Running late. I don't know.
大忙人  现在是联邦检察官对吗
Busy man. Federal prosecutor now, right?
对  听上去挺厉害
Yeah, it's very fancy.
他那里  马特
Oh, there he is. Matt.
你真的是个警察吗
You sure you're really a cop?
好了  马特  这是汉克·博伊特警长
Okay, Matt, this is Sergeant Hank Voight.
也是我上司  你注意点
Otherwise known as my boss so be nice.
幸会  警长
Nice to meet you, Sergeant.
叫汉克就行  你们好好玩
Hank. All right, have fun.
很抱歉我迟到了  今天忙疯了
I'm sorry I'm late. It's just been a crazy day.
在处理反诈骗集团的案子  热度很高所以...
I'm in the middle of that RICO case, and it's heating up so...
我知道你要说什么  工作太忙了
Oh, I knew how this goes: too much work.
忙死了  没空谈恋爱
Too busy, no time for a relationship.
这样看待这事就很不愉快啦
Wow, well, that's a jaded way to look at it.
是吗  那你觉得要怎样浪漫积极地看待
Oh, yeah? What's the rosy, optimistic way?
我可是在一生中最重要的调查过程中
The fact that I didn't cancel tonight in the middle
没有取消今晚的约会
of the most important investigation of my life
现在可是拿下奥德萨黑帮的关键时候
on the cusp of taking down the Odessa mob
这还不能表明你有多重要吗
is an obvious indication of how important you are to me.
-真会说  -我知道
- Ooh, you're good. - I know.
谢谢各位的到来
Thank you all for coming.
也谢谢我们的主人杰森·卡西迪
And thank you to our host, Jason Cassidy,
将他美丽的家与我们分享
for opening up his lovely home.
我正在竞选连任  这大家都知道
I am running for re-election. That's no secret.
芝加哥的名声大家也知道
Neither is Chicago's reputation.
我们经历了艰难的时期
We have fallen on hard times.
芝加哥警署也遭到攻击
Quite simply the Chicago Police Department is under fire.
而我们不能攻击他们  应该支持他们
Rather than attacking them, we should be supporting them.
因为他们工作做得很棒
Because they are the best in the business.
我最清楚这一点
I know that first hand.
作为一名检察官  我和这些
As a prosecutor, I have worked alongside
无私勇敢的人一起共事了很多年
these selfless and courageous folks for years.
比如我的朋友  汉克·博伊特警长
Like my friend, Sergeant Hank Voight.
毫无疑问
Make no mistake.
这些勇敢的人
These brave men and women
将会继续
are and will continue to be
我们城市的守护天使
our precious city's saving grace.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我不想打扰你
I don't want to bother you with this,
但得让你知道
but I'm just giving you a head's up.
-内务部刚刚给我打电话  -什么事
- I just got a call from IAD. - About what?
翻译     西之   风城章鱼X   H小欠
关于我卧底的时候在酒吧打的架
About the fight at the bar when I was undercover.
绑架案  谁知道这事
The kidnapping case? Who knew about that?
翻译     小萝莉   Lynn_宁   pang   圈圈
厄普顿  阿特沃特  我们用的两个缉毒警
Upton, Atwater, the two narcotics cops we used,
还有鲁塞克  是他写的报告
and Ruzek. He wrote the paper on it.
校对     圈圈
但我知道他报告上
But I know for a fact that he didn't put anything
没有说到这个案子
in the case report about it.
别想太复杂了
Just keep it simple.
时间轴     西查   chance-coco
你在卧底  打架了
You were undercover. Fight broke out.
一个人拿着啤酒瓶朝你冲过来
Guy rushed at you with a beer bottle.
你担心受到直接伤害
You were in fear of imminent bodily harm
后期     8T
所以你就自卫了  等等
so you defended yourself. Hold on.
我是博伊特
Voight.
现在吗
Right now?
总监     圈圈
我这就过去
I'm on my way.
有什么事吗
Everything okay?
我只是...
I'm just...
我得问一句  你没有报告
I got to ask, you didn't file
那次打架的事吧
anything about the fight, did you?
你是真心在问吗
Are you seriously asking me that?
我没觉得你会报告  我就是问一下
I didn't think so. I just wanted to check.
我觉得发生了这么多事
Look, I think after everything that happened
你该考虑和谁谈一谈
you should consider talking to somebody.
不用了
I'm good.
谢谢建议
Thanks for the suggestion.
你确定吗  事态挺严重的
You sure? Things got pretty intense.
我们救了一个孩子  这才是最重要的
We saved a kid's life. That's all that matters.
我同意  但你得确定
Yeah, I agree, but you just want to make sure
不会引发别的事
that nothing got triggered.
海莉  谢谢你关心我
Hailey, I appreciate you looking out for me.
真的
I do, really.
我没事  不需要保姆
I'm fine, and I don't need a babysitter.
明白
Copy you.
好  什么情况
All right, what do we know so far?
有人投诉
Somebody complained
说有闹钟一直没关掉
that there was an alarm clock that wouldn't shut off
所以酒店经理就敲门了
so a hotel manager knocked on the door,
没人开门  他就打开了门
didn't get a response, and when he opened it
发现一个女孩死了
he found a dead girl
床上还有一个昏迷的男客人
and a male guest passed out on the bed.
-枪呢  -九毫米口径
- Gun? - Nine millimeter.
就在床边上
It was there next to the bed.
男客呢
Where's the male guest now?
在这里  警长
In here, Sarge.
议员
Congressman.
我知道这事看起来是什么样  汉克  但...
I know what this looks like, Hank, but...
不是我干的
I didn't do it.
我发誓
I swear to God.
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第八集
受害人是无名氏
Victim's a Jane Doe.
指纹查不到  也没有电话记录
Prints weren't in the system. No cell phone.
只有他们在她钱包里
Only thing they found in her purse
发现了一份假的驾照
was a fake driver's license.
上面的名字是亚斯名·莫尔特
The name on it was Yasmine Molt.
我们会去查查看有什么线索
We'll run it. We'll see if anything hits.
枪有什么线索吗
Anything on the gun?
没登记过  装了消音器
Unregistered. Suppresser attached.
序列号被毁掉了
And the serial number was defaced.
上面只有格雷诺的指纹
The only print they lifted off of it was Graynor's.
-手上有弹药残留吗  -没有  但是
- GSR on his hands? - Negative, but you know what?
他可能在巡警到之前洗了手
He could have washed up before patrol got there.
16发子弹  假设是装满了的
16 round mag, assuming it was full,
至少开了两枪
at least two bullets were fired.
对  但受害人只有一处枪伤
Yeah, the victim was only shot once.
-发现另一颗子弹了吗  -没有
- Did you find the other bullet? - Mm-mm, no.
-也没有弹壳  -查弹道
- No shell casings either. - Run ballistics.
谁知道呢  也许和其它犯罪有关系
Who knows, maybe it will connect to another crime.
好的
Okay.
从头开始  斯科特
Start at the beginning, Scott.
和我们回顾一下
Just walk us through what happened.
我从派对上回来
I came back from the party.
在酒店酒吧喝了点酒
I had a drink at the hotel bar.
看了几封邮件
Started going through some emails
这个年轻姑娘就开始和我搭话
and then this young lady started talking to me.
你知道她的名字吗
You get her name?
我记得她说她叫亚斯名
I think she said it was Yasmine.
-是妓女吗  -可能是
- Hooker? - Possible.
她有口音
She had an accent.
大概是东欧  俄罗斯那一块的
It was eastern European, maybe Russian.
那你们都说了什么
So what you guys talk about?
不确定
Not sure.
怎么会不确定呢
Well, explain that to me.
我的记忆  模糊了
My memory's... blurry.
那你记得邀请她去你的房间吗
You remember inviting her to your room?
不记得  我无法想象会邀请她  我
No, but I can't imagine that I really did. I...
我不会背叛我的妻子
I don't cheat on my wife,
是的  我知道现在听起来很可笑
and yes, I know that sounds absurd given the circumstances.
她肯定趁我去洗手间的时候给我下了药
She must have drugged me when I got up to go to the restroom.
只有这样才能说得通
That is the only thing that makes sense.
我以前从来没有这样断片过
I have never blacked out before.
好吧  那么
Okay, so...
她给你下了药  你们上了楼
She drugged you. You went upstairs.
然后你昏过去了
Then you passed out,
你们俩之外的第三个人进来  把她打死
and some guy other than you comes in, shoots the girl,
把枪放在你的手里  让枪上布满你的指纹
puts the gun in your hand, gets your fingerprints all over it,
然后把枪扔到地上走出去了
then tosses the gun on the ground and walks out.
这故事可够玄的  斯科特
That's a hell of a theory, Scott.
肯定有人陷害我
Somebody must have set me up.
只有这一种可能性
It is the only plausible explanation
才能解释这种荒谬的局面
to this totally implausible situation.
你觉得有什么人可能陷害你
Any idea who might want to do that?
-多到数不清  -怎么说
- Too many to count. - How's that?
我投票反对一项重大建设计划
I voted against a major construction project
就在53区
in the 53rd Ward.
然后那项计划流产了
And after that the deal fell apart.
因此遭受了损失的人就盯上了我
Then the people who lost out came after me.
有在网上骂我的  有划我轮胎的
There was verbal attacks on social media, slashed tires.
城里的每一个建筑商  工会代表和市议员
Every builder and union rep and alderman in this city
都希望我出事
would love to see me fail.
几位  格雷诺众议员
Look, guys, Congressman Graynor
显然需要休息  我想他可以走了吧
clearly needs some rest. I assume he's free to go?
我们还得再多拘留他一阵子
We're gonna keep him in custody
等我们把事情查清楚
a little longer until we can clear this up.
你就放心  斯科特  让我们去查
Just sit tight, Scott. Let us do our job.
我们会把事情查个水落石出的
We'll figure out what the hell really happened here.
除非你们逮捕他
Unless he's under arrest,
我们现在就走
we're walking out of here.
不  不用  麦克
No, it's all right, Mike.
我相信博伊特警长
I trust Sergeant Voight.
该做什么就做  我坦坦荡荡
Do what you need to do. I got nothing to hide.
我唯一的要求就是
The only thing I ask is...
别泄露给媒体
keep this out of the press.
我尽量  不过
I'll do my best but...
证据对你很不利  所以我也不好说
the evidence goes against you, all bets are off.
这是昨晚的一段监控录像
This is a feed from last night.
你们的人在吧台这里
There's your man at the bar.
格雷诺看起来挺高兴的
Well, Graynor seems to be enjoying himself.
是啊
Hell yeah.
-等等  怎么回事  -不知道
- Wait, wait, what happened? - No idea.
能麻烦你快进一下吗
can you fast forward that for me?
看看有多长时间没录上
Let's see how long it stays off.
10点2分失去画面  10点46分恢复
Okay, went out at 10:02. Came back online at 10:46.
正好是那位无名女被杀的时间
Same time the Jane Doe was murdered.
是啊  未免也太巧了
Yeah, that is a hell of a coincidence.
昨晚是谁在值班
You know who was on duty last night?
一个叫卢克·艾维的男的
Guy named Luke Ivey.
他在我们这干了三年了
He's been with us for about three years,
但他是个挺温和的人
but he's a pretty mellow guy.
想象不到他会干这种事
Can't imagine he's involved in this.
好吧  我们需要
All right, well, we're gonna need
这个人的联络方式
his contact information right now.
这些大麻我都是有处方的
I got a medical prescription for the weed,
所以完全合法
so it's totally legit.
我们不是来问你的大麻的
We're not here about your weed.
我们要问你昨晚的事
We're actually here about last night.
昨晚是你在班布里奇安保执勤吧
You were working security at the Bainbridge, right?
对  我听说有个女的被杀了
Oh, right. I heard a girl got killed or something?
是  而且案发那段时间  监控摄像
Yeah, and it just so happens that the surveillance system
恰好停止工作了
was shut down at the time of the murder.
你了解是什么原因吗
Yeah, you know anything about that?
你觉得是有人故意
You think somebody intentionally
关掉了安保监控
shut down the security system?
我们是这么考虑过
It crossed our minds, yes.
你是在10点到11点当值吧
You were working between 10:00 and 11:00, right?
是啊  断断续续的
Yeah, on and off.
我一半时间都在里屋
I spent half the time in the back room,
看电视上的格斗比赛
watching a fight on TV.
卢克  你见过这个女的吗
Luke, you ever seen this woman?
-认识她吗  -不认识
- You recognize her? - No.
没见过  她就是死者吗
Never. She the one that got killed?
你听着  问问题的是我们
Listen, the way this works is that we ask the questions,
-你只管回答  -抱歉
- you answer. - Sorry.
我的错  尽管问吧
My bad. Ask away.
好  所以你没有关闭监控
All right, so you didn't shut it down.
你知道谁有可能吗
Do you know who did?
谁都有可能啊
Could have been anyone.
好多人都有权限进入监控室
Lots of people have access to that room.
-斯科特·格雷诺  -是
- Scott Graynor? - Yeah.
-我知道他  -你喜欢他吗
- Yeah, I know him. - You like him?
不  他是个右翼种族主义混蛋
No. He's a racist, right-wing prick.
我不确定我是不是同意
I'm not sure I agree with that,
但这不是我来的原因  雷
but that's not why I'm here, Ray.
那你有何贵干啊
So why are you here?
私下里说  我们是来查一件涉及他的凶杀案
Off the record, we're looking at him for a homicide.
案情有点奇怪
The facts are a bit odd.
不过格雷诺说不是他做的  说有人陷害他
But Graynor claims he didn't do it, thinks he was set up.
有这个可能
That is possible.
斯科特在这里可不怎么受欢迎
Ol' Scott isn't too popular around here,
至少眼下是这样
not right now anyway.
是啊  我听说那个建设案的事了
Yeah, I mean, I heard about the construction deal.
对  多功能市中小区
Yeah, mixed-use, urban village,
餐厅  公寓和办公室
cafes, apartments, offices--
本来是利在千秋的好事
it would've been a game-changer.
那是怎么回事
All right, what happened?
格雷诺把联邦拨款调到别的地方去了
Graynor redirected all the federal dollars elsewhere.
还说什么他希望把更多的投资分配给
Gave some half-assed speech about how he wanted
更外围郊区之类的蠢话
more investments in more rural areas.
真相就是这个人根本不相信
The truth is the man doesn't believe
重振市区的计划
in urban revitalization.
他想在我的选区里建的
The only thing he wants to build in my ward
只有监狱
is a damn prison.
所以格雷诺说他
So Graynor's telling the truth
-有很多敌人是真的  -是啊
- about having a lot of enemies. - Yeah.
太对了
You're damn right.
知道有谁可能最恨他吗
Any idea who might be at the top of the list?
比尔·马哈尼
Bill Mahoney.
他是钢铁工人联合会的主席
He's the head of the Iron Workers Union.
谢了  雷
Appreciate it, Ray.
毫不意外  死因是子弹
No surprise, C.O.D. is exsanguination
射入胸膛导致的大量失血
to do with the bullet entering her chest.
有性活动的迹象吗
Any evidence of sexual activity?
没有  也没发现第三方的基因痕迹
None. No traces of third-party DNA, either.
不过我确实发现她的上臂植入了这个
But I did find this implanted in her upper arm.
还真不是每天能见到的东西
You don't see this every day.
法医在无名女的胳膊里找到了卫星定位芯片
M.E. found a GPS chip in Jane Doe's arm.
像那种植到心爱的宠物身上的东西
Like something you put in a prized pet.
可惜我们追踪不了
Unfortunately, we can't track it.
-有人在追踪她  -是  可能是拉皮条的
- Someone was tracking her. - Yeah, probably the pimp.
凶杀
被害人  无名女
这个拉皮条的是老手啊
That's a pretty sophisticated pimp.
毒性报告出来了
Hey, tox report came back.
格雷诺没错  他被下药了
Graynor was right, about the drugs anyways.
他们在他血液里发现了氯胺酮和羟二氢可待因酮
They found Ketamine and Oxy in his blood.
所以他才会晕过去
Well, that explains the blacking out.
是的  但现在的问题就是下药的是他自己
Yeah, but now the question is did he drug himself?
-还是别人  -我不知道
- Or was he drugged? - I don't know,
就算他自己吃了药  也解释不通
even if he took the drugs himself, it still doesn't make sense.
这次枪击是有预谋的  枪上装了消音器
This shooting was premeditated. The gun had a silencer.
人在那种状态下杀人的几率呢
The odds of someone doing a murder in that state of mind?
-很小  -是的  我同意
- Pretty remote. - Yeah, I agree.
要么格雷诺是世上最蠢的罪犯
Either Graynor is the dumbest criminal ever
要么就是有人陷害他
or somebody set him up.
嫌疑人
格雷诺  斯科特
铁和金属机械工会
比尔·马哈尼  你好啊
Bill Mahoney, how you doing?
需要问你几个问题
Just need to ask you a few questions.
-关于什么  -议员格雷诺
- About what? - Congressman Graynor.
他死了还是怎么了
Did he wind up dead or something?
这个回答有点意思啊
Well, that's an interesting response.
我很忙  到底是什么事
I'm busy. What the hell is this about?
你能告诉我们你昨晚在哪里吗
Do you mind telling us where you were last night?
-能  -我们很乐意带你去警局
- Yes. - Well, we're happy to take you down
如果你想去的话
to the station if you prefer.
你们要跟我说说这是怎么回事吗
You gonna tell me what this is about?
调查显示你是一件凶杀案的嫌疑人
Your name came up as a person of interest in a homicide.
-现在我只能说到这  -凶杀案
- That's all I can say right now. - Homicide?
你们觉得我跟谋杀有关
You think I'm involved in some murder?
-疯了吧  -好的
- That's crazy. - Okay.
那就告诉我们你昨晚在哪里
So tell us where you were last night
十点到十点半
between 10:00 and 10:30.
在医院
At the hospital.
我妹妹生孩子
My sister had a baby girl.
吉莉安
Jillian.
五斤重
Six pounds, nine ounces.
母女平安  谢谢你们关心
Mom and baby are doing great, thanks for asking.
要是没什么事我先走了
Now, if there's nothing else...
马哈尼的不在场证明没问题
Mahoney's alibi checks out.
晚上十点到早上三点他都在芝加哥医院
He was at Chicago Med from 10:00 pm to 3:00 am.
所以又要回到格雷诺身上
Which brings us back to Graynor.
我不知道
I don't know.
无论你同不同意他的政见  他历史清白
Whether or not you agree with his politics, he's clean.
西北人  在海军服过役
Northwestern. Served in the marines.
经常去教堂  结婚十七年有两个孩子
Active in his church. Married 17 years with two kids.
是的  因为会去教堂的男人不会出轨
Yeah, 'cause church-going men never cheat on their wives.
好吧  那无名女呢
All right, what about our Jane Doe?
-有新线索吗  -我跟拉皮条的线人聊过
- We find anything new? - I talked to a pimp CI.
他不认识她  但他说
He couldn't ID her, but he said there are
有很多东欧姑娘在黄金海岸的酒店工作
lots of Eastern European girls working the Gold Coast hotels.
也跟格雷诺的口供相符
Which jibes with Graynor's story.
-他说那个姑娘有口音  -谢谢
- He said the girl had an accent. - Thanks.
杀死无名女的枪
The gun that killed our Jane Doe
跟另一件枪击案有关  女性  近四十岁
just showed up in another shooting, a woman, late 30s.
昨晚有人在离班布里奇两条街的地方
Someone found her in a car last night
发现她在车里中了枪
two blocks from the Bainbridge.
-她能撑过来吗  -能
- She going to make it? - Yeah.
刚刚出手术室  情况稳定
She just got out of surgery. She's in stable condition.
我们走
Let's go.
她叫伊琳娜·佩卓娃
Her name's Irina Petrova.
还是有点虚弱
Still a little groggy,
一直在问她女儿
keeps asking about her daughter.
谢谢
Thanks.
好的
Okay.
女士  我是汉克·博伊特警长
Ma'am. I'm Sergeant Hank Voight.
这位是奥林斯基警探
This is Detective Olinsky.
我们想问你几个问题
We want to ask you a couple of questions.
我女儿还好吗
Is my daughter okay?
-你女儿  -是的
- Your daughter? - Yes.
萨莎  我很担心她
Sasha. I'm very worried about her.
这就是无名女
That's our Jane Doe.
女士  很遗憾  你女儿死了
Ma'am, I'm so sorry. Your daughter's dead.
萨莎
Sasha?
她被杀了吗
She's murdered?
恐怕是的
I'm afraid so.
我应该知道他是谁
I think I know who he is.
杀她的人
The man who killed her.
太好了  他是谁
That's great. Who is he?
之前有个男人
A man came
找我女儿和她朋友做模特
and offered my daughter and her friend modeling contracts.
她们就来了芝加哥
So they came here to Chicago.
我三个月没有她的音信
Three months I hadn't heard from her.
我一直给她打电话
And I called and called.
然后两周前  我收到一条短信
And then two weeks ago, I got a message.
萨莎说她被...
Sasha said she was...
软禁了
a hostage.
说这个人拿走了她的护照和钱
That this man took her passport and money
而且他会监视她的一举一动
and that he was watching her every move.
你做了什么
Well, what'd you do?
我买了机票  只身过来
I bought a ticket, and I came here myself.
她是我女儿
She's my daughter.
我知道这很难  但是...
I know this is hard, but...
你觉得你能认出对你开枪的人吗
Do you think you could identify the man who shot you?
他不在这里
He's not here.
他更年轻  光头
He was younger and bald.
而且他是乌克兰人
And he was Ukrainian.
-你怎么知道  -他叫我"嗦咔"
- How do you know that? - He called me "Sooka."
在他对我开枪之前
Before he shot me.
意思是贱人
That means bitch.
妈妈拿着她女儿萨莎的照片
The mom canvassed the Ukrainian village
在乌克兰村到处问
with a photo of her daughter Sasha.
发现一个在杂货店上班的人认识她
Found some guy works at a grocery store recognized her.
她和别的姑娘都在那里买吃的
Apparently, she and the other girls buy food there.
是的  所以伊琳娜给了那人一百块
Yeah, so Irina paid the guy 100 bucks
把一次性手机塞进了她买的东西里
to smuggle a burner phone into her groceries.
萨莎和她妈妈短信联系  制定了逃跑计划
Sasha texts her mom and they hatch an escape plan.
但她们还没来得及实施就有人发现了手机
But someone found the phone before they could pull it off.
各位
Hey, guys.
有发现
I got something.
我在离班布里奇两条街远的监控录像上
All right, I pulled this from a security camera
找到了这个
two blocks away from the Bainbridge.
那是伊琳娜在她租来的车上
That's Irina in her rental car.
看时间  十点二十二
Look at the time stamp. 10:22.
差不多就是萨莎被杀的时间
It's around the same time Sasha was killed.
是的  但他想先去杀了妈妈
Yeah, but first he tries taking out the mom.
所以他给伊琳娜来了一枪  然后去酒店
So he shoots Irina, and then he walks over to the hotel
杀了她女儿
and he kills her daughter.
好  把这个画面放大
All right, blow that image up,
看看能不能对这位秃头朋友进行面部识别
see if we get a hit on facial rec of our bald friend.
如果不行  就把照片放出去
If not, get the picture out on the streets.
我要找到这龟孙子
I want to find this son of a bitch.
我刚刚跟抢劫凶案组聊了聊
Hey, so I just talked to Robbery-Homicide.
近半年来有一群
There's a ring of Eastern European women
北欧女人在万艾可三角区
that have been active in the Viagra Triangle
很活跃
over the last six months.
是的  我拉皮条的线人也这么说
Yeah, my pimp CI said the same thing.
但她们不是妓女  而是正儿八经的小偷
But they're not hookers. They're identity thieves.
目标是高端酒店的富人
They target wealthy men in high-end hotels.
给他们下药  复制信用卡  偷手表
Drug them, clone their credit cards, steal watches,
现金  一切她们能够拿到的东西
loose cash, whatever they can grab.
幕后主使是奥德萨黑帮
The scam is run by the Odessa mob.
这就说得通了
That makes sense.
萨莎和她朋友是从
Sasha and her friend were recruited
那附近的村庄里招来的
from a village not far from there.
查了格雷诺的信用卡了吗
Hey, you run Graynor's credit cards yet?
查了
Yeah.
4张卡都刷爆了
All four were maxed out,
昨天开始的  所有消费
and starting yesterday, all the charges
都在东欧
originated in Eastern Europe.
可以走了  斯科特
Free to go, Scott.
-找到凶手了吗  -我们有了几条确凿的线索
- You found the killer? - We got a few solid leads.
我们知道那个
We do know you're not responsible
年轻姑娘的死和你无关
for what happened to that young lady.
感谢你说出来
I appreciate you saying that out loud.
还是不敢相信这一切真发生了
I still can't believe this really happened.
你从这边出去
Listen, I want you to go out this way.
这里通向后巷
It leads to a back alley.
我打给你的律师了  他在等你
I called your lawyer. He's waiting for you.
所以没人知道这事吗
So no one knows about any of this?
对
No.
谢谢  汉克
I appreciate that, Hank.
你是个信守承诺的人
Man of his word.
非常难得
Rare commodity.
至少在我的行业里很少见
In my business anyway.
谢谢  发生了什么事
Thank you. So what's going on?
听上去挺重要
It sounded important.
你要在咖啡车边和我分手吗
Are you breaking up with me at the coffee cart?
我不会在咖啡车边和你分手
I wouldn't break up with you at a coffee cart.
拜托  那也太有格调了
Come on, I'm too classy for that.
我们在查的一个案子
Uh, no, there's a case we're investigating that
可能和你眼下在查的事有交叉
I think might intersect with the one you're working on.
我在面部识别系统里查遍了  都没线索
I ran it through facial recognition, didn't get a hit.
觉得你可能认得这人
I'm thinking you might recognize the guy.
-什么案子  -凶杀案
- What's the case? - Homicide.
受害者是年轻的乌克兰姑娘
Young Ukrainian woman.
这家伙是头号嫌犯
This guy's our prime suspect.
我们觉得他和奥德萨黑帮有关
And we think that he's connected to the Odessa mob.
对
Right.
你知道他是谁吗
Hey. Do you know who he is?
-我不能说  -为什么
- I can't answer that. - Why not?
我现在能说的是他是我们
All I can say right now is he's a person of interest
调查案件的嫌犯
in the case we're investigating.
我们这边也是  而且是谋杀案
Yeah, us too, and it's a murder
所以我确定我们会赢
so I'm pretty sure that we win.
没那么简单
Yeah, it's not that simple.
我得和一些人谈谈这事
Okay, uh, I need to talk to a few people about this,
你该和博伊特谈谈
and you should talk to Voight.
我觉得我们该一起坐下聊聊
I think we should all sit down
找出最好的推进方法
and figure out the best way to move forward.
我们是一个战队的  对吧
We're on the same team, right?
如果你知道这个人...
If you know who this guy is--
金  这很重要  拜托
Kim. It's important, please.
去和博伊特聊聊  好吗
Just talk to Voight, okay?
我会准备个会议  我们从那里开始谈
I'm gonna set up a meeting. We'll go from there.
相信我好吗
Hey, would you just trust me?
我是在保护我们  好吗
I'm protecting both of us, okay?
好的
Got it.
回头打给你  好吗
I'll call you later, okay?
你和你男朋友说了我们的案件
You talked to your boyfriend about our case?
马特在调查奥德萨黑帮
Well, Matt is investigating the Odessa mob.
他们在查一个反诈骗集团案
They're building the RICO case.
所以我觉得他可能
So I thought he might be able
会认出这个谋杀案里的嫌犯
to identify the suspect in our homicide.
我猜猜  他并没帮上忙
Let me guess...he couldn't.
对  他觉得我们可以见个面
No, he thought that we should meet
聊聊最好的推进方法
and discuss the best way to proceed.
我想帮忙的  警长
I was trying to help, Sergeant.
我们需要枪手的名字
We needed the name of the shooter.
我觉得他会知道  所以是的
I thought he might know, and so yes,
-我跟他说了案件  -金
- I told him about our case. - Look, Kim.
你和谁睡我管不着
I could give a damn who you sleep with,
但我很在意
but I care a whole hell of a lot
你把我们的机密和谁共享
who you share our information with.
我以为他能帮上忙
I thought he could help us.
联邦政府人员内部互助而已  只会是这样
The Feds help the Feds. That's it, end of story.
进来
Come in.
-我查到了线索  -是什么
- I got something. - What is it?
从上个月到现在的监控中
Been looking at surveillance video from the past month.
发现了萨莎和酒吧的枪手
Found footage of Sasha and the bald guy,
秃头男的镜头
the shooter from the bar.
而且看到了他和我们的好朋友
And I just found a shot of him
卢克·艾维在一起的镜头
with our good friend, Luke Ivey.
安保人员
Security guy.
那个瘾君子撒谎了
That pothead was lying to us.
带他过来  马上
Get his ass in here. Now.
-就这样  -好的
- All right. - Okay.
门没锁
We got an open door.
卢克
Hey, Luke.
Luke.
卢克  你在哪
Luke. Where you at, man?
我们是芝加哥警署
Hey. Hey, Chicago PD.
举起手
Get your hands up.
卢克
Hey, Luke.
该死
Son of a bitch.
我叫人来
I'll go call it in.
该死
Damn it.
艾维头后方正中一枪  近距离的
Ivey took one right to the back of the head, close range.
有闯入的迹象吗
Any sign of a break-in?
没有  没有打斗痕迹  是快速作案
No, sir. No struggle. Straight execution.
我和邻居聊了
I spoke to a neighbor.
她说听到了枪声
She said she heard a gunshot.
看到窗外有一个白人  秃头男
Looked out the window, saw a white, bald guy
上了辆黑色奔驰
get into a black Mercedes.
她没能记下车牌
She couldn't get the plates though.
给她看监控里的照片了吗
You show her the surveillance photo?
看了  她很确定是同一个人
Yeah, she says she's pretty positive it was him.
所以这家伙开始紧张了
So our guy gets nervous.
把他在酒店的接应干掉了  这说得通
Dumps his inside man at the hotel. Makes sense.
是伯吉斯
Burgess.
我和联调局的人得见个面
I got a meeting with the FBI.
他们现在要帮我们了
The Feds helping us out?
我说见个面
I said I had a meeting.
我没说帮忙
I didn't say anything about getting any help.
就像我和金说的那样  考虑到潜在的矛盾
Like I told Kim, given the potential conflicts here,
我们应该一起确定一下方向
it makes sense for all of us to get on the same page.
在我看来  警长
So, from my understanding, Sergeant,
你的小队在调查一起谋杀案
your Unit is investigating a homicide
可能和奥德萨黑帮相关
that may be connected to the Odessa mob.
实际上  是两起凶杀案  但金只是推断
Actually, it's two homicides, but Kim was just speculating.
我们没有证据证实他和黑帮有关
We don't have any evidence connecting him to this group.
我们确定  我认得金给我看的照片上的人
We do. I recognized the photo Kim showed me.
他是底层的  运作一些网络诈骗环节
He's a low level player, runs their cyber-fraud division.
那太好了  他叫什么名字
That's great. Just give me his name.
我们会把他挖出来  帮你省事了
We'll scoop him up. Save you the trouble.
你也说了  他是个底层的混混
Well, you said yourself, he's just a low-level punk.
我们不能说
We can't reveal that information.
现在不行
Not at this point in time.
我们调查这些混蛋两年了
We've been investigating these pricks for two years.
马上就能拿下他们整个组织了
We're this close to taking down the whole damn organization.
我们不想打草惊蛇
And we don't want to spook anyone.
我们得让他们觉得一切如常
We need them to think everything's normal.
我们明白  你们追这条线很久了
Look, we get it. You've been working this a long time-- -
但等这个案子结束  我们会告诉你们一切
But when the case is over we'll give you everything you need
帮你们抓住这个混蛋
to nail this son of a bitch.
我保证
I give you my word on that.
问题是
The thing is, guys,
我手头的案子是个被杀害的18岁女孩
I got a dead girl, 18 years old.
我觉得她妈不关心你们的反诈骗集团案
And I highly doubt her mother gives a damn about your RICO case.
我明白  我明白  我真的明白
I get it, I get it. I really do.
但是就像我之前说的
But like I said before,
我们不能让一个地方上的案子影响到调查
we can't let a local case interfere with this investigation.
你是让我什么都不要做吗
You asking me to sit on my hands?
是的  只是暂时的
Yes. Just for the time being.
好吧  你赢了
Okay, you win.
谢谢你们如此理解我们的工作
Thank you for being so understanding.
-是啊  -我们很感激
- Yeah. - We appreciate it.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了  好消息是  我们现在知道
All right, the good news is, we now know
我们的嫌疑人是奥德萨黑帮的人
our suspect is part of the Odessa mob.
给安东尼奥打电话  让人去查那乌克兰村
Call Antonio, get boots on the ground in Ukrainian Village.
分发萨莎和那个男性嫌疑人的照片
Circulate the photo of Sasha and that male suspect.
相信我  有人会知道的  所以...
Believe me, someone's gonna know so...
等一下  你刚说在他们搞定他们的案子前
Wait, you just said we were gonna stand down
-我们什么都不做  -听着  金  你有机会
- until they made their case. - Listen, Kim, you got a chance
能破获一件谋杀案  不要等  把案子破了
to make a murder case, you make it; you don't wait.
所以继续调查
So the investigation is still on?
假装刚刚的会面没有发生
We're gonna pretend like that meeting didn't happen?
有问题吗
Is that a problem?
-没有  -什么都不要和马特说  听到了吗
- No. - So keep your mouth shut around Matt, you hear me?
-什么都别说  -知道了
- Not a word. - Yeah, I hear you.
好了  去医院
All right, head over to the hospital,
给伊琳娜看一下监控录象
show Irina that surveillance video.
也许她能认出她女儿的朋友
Maybe she can ID her daughter's friend.
你能看一下这个吗
Do you mind taking a look at this?
我来
I got it.
是萨莎被害那晚的录像
It's from the night that Sasha was killed.
她那么漂亮
She was so beautiful.
抱歉得让你看这个
I'm sorry to make you watch it.
你告诉博伊特警长
You told Sergeant Voight
萨莎是和一个朋友一起来芝加哥的
that Sasha came to Chicago with a friend.
是  奥林·泽林可
Yes, Olene Zelenko.
奥林
Olene.
你在录像里看到奥林了吗
Do you see Olene anywhere in this video?
-这个就是奥林  -好的
- There, that's Olene. - Okay.
谢谢  那对我们很有帮助
Thank you. That's very helpful.
你要去救她吗
Are you going to rescue her?
我们会努力的
We're gonna try.
我们会把这张照片给在酒店工作的人看
We're gonna show this photo to people who work at hotels.
希望有人见过她  能帮我们找到她
Hopefully, someone's seen her, can help us find her.
当我们找到奥林的时候  希望她能帮我们
And then once we find Olene, hopefully she can help us
找到杀害萨莎的凶手
find the man that killed Sasha.
-谢谢  -应该的
- Thank you. - Yeah.
她的名字是奥林·泽林可
Her name's Olene Zelenko.
她被奥德萨黑帮控制住了
She's being held captive by the Odessa mob.
她在黄金海岸的各种高档酒店
She's doing ID thefts at various high-end hotels
失踪人口
进行身份盗窃  所以我们就在那用这照片找人
on the Gold Coast so let's get these photos out there.
行动
Now.
谢了  特鲁迪
Thanks, Trudy.
没什么
No problem.
我听说你和你的新情郎之间的问题了
I heard about your issue with your new beau.
没什么的
It's not an issue.
那很好  因为你应该小心点
Right, good. 'Cause you should be careful.
那是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
意思是事情变得复杂了
It means things get complicated.
我们和联调局做的是同样的工作
We do the same job as the Feds,
但是我们不是一边的
but we are not on the same team.
所以你如果真的很喜欢这家伙的话
So if you really like this guy,
-也许你想要离远点  -离什么远点
- you might want to step away. - Step away from what?
这案子
The case.
不
No.
不用这样  不过谢谢了
I'm good, but thanks.
好吧
Okay.
传言你排除了我最喜欢的议员的嫌疑
So, the word is you've moved off my favorite congressman.
你比我想的还要消息灵通
You're even more connected than I thought.
问题是  汉克
Here's the problem, Hank.
我的开发商朋友告诉我
My developer friends have told me
他们还对西区的工程很感兴趣
they're still interested in the West Side project.
但问题是我们需要格雷诺的支持
But the problem is we need Graynor on board.
-那和他说啊  -是啊
- Then talk to him. - Yeah.
-就在这  -我都说了大概20次了
- Right here. - I have about 20 times.
那家伙就是不上道
The man just doesn't believe in it.
他有权坚持自己的意见
He's entitled to his opinion.
但不能是在对我的工作不利的时候
Not when it's bad for business--my business.
你们两个意见不一致
Look, you two don't see eye to eye.
和我没关系
It's got nothing to do with me.
当然有
Sure it does.
怎么说
How's that?
你欠我的
You owe me a favor.
那个爱尔兰警察的事我可什么都没说
I kept my mouth shut about that Irish cop.
麦克格雷迪  你记得吗
McGrady. You remember him?
记得
I do.
自杀嫁祸给那个年轻兄弟
Framed that young brother for his own suicide.
真够可以的
Hell of a thing.
别担心  汉克
Don't worry, Hank.
我什么都没说
I didn't say a word.
我只是坐在那里看着
I just sat there and watched.
你们都悲伤地向他致敬
All you boys in blue saluting his ass,
像对待什么英雄似的
treating him like some damn hero.
你想要什么
What's the ask?
我要一张照片
I want a picture.
什么照片
What picture?
犯罪现场的照片
The crime scene photo.
格雷诺和那个死去的女孩的照片
Of Graynor and the dead girl.
我告诉过你了  他是无辜的
I already told you, he's innocent.
是  他没有犯谋杀罪  但他还是在场
Yeah, of murder, but he was still there.
他是受害者
He was a mark.
谁在乎呢
Who gives a damn?
公众看到一个妓女
The public sees that picture of a dead hooker
死在他的酒店房间  天
in his hotel room, hell.
教皇都无能为力了
The damn Pope couldn't get out from under that.
见到你很高兴  雷
It was good to see you, Ray.
普莱斯想要犯罪现场的照片
Price wants to see crime scene photos.
是啊  这样他就可以毁掉格雷诺了
Yeah, so he can blow up Graynor.
想要在他的选区做一些好看的业绩
Wants to build some sort of fancy office project in his ward.
-告诉他没门  -我也想
- Just tell him to go to hell. - I wish I could.
我不知道他有我们的把柄
I didn't know he had a marker.
是啊  还是挺严重的把柄
Yeah, it's a pretty good one.
我喜欢格雷诺
I like Graynor.
我也喜欢  坦白正直的人
Yeah, so do I. Straight shooter.
支持警察  我也喜欢他
Supports the police. I like him, too.
也许普莱斯是在虚张声势
Maybe, uh, Price is bluffing?
也许吧  也有可能  但是...
Maybe, it's possible, but...
如果不是  那破坏力就大了
If he's not, he can do a lot of damage.
他可能会让有的人丢了工作
He may ruin a few careers.
刚刚跟兰斯顿酒店经理打完电话
Just got off the phone with the manager at the Langston hotel.
他刚才说到奥林和一个中年商人
He said he just saw Olene get into an elevator
进了电梯
with a middle-aged businessman.
-可信吗  -可信
- Sound credible? - Yeah.
他说她有口音并且和我们给他的
He said she has an accent and has the same dress
奥林照片上的人穿着同样的裙子
Olene was wearing in the picture we sent over.
好的  带上安东尼奥  去看看
All right, grab Antonio. Check it out.
好的
Okay.
她一个小时前和两个女孩一起出现在这里
She showed up about an hour ago with two other girls.
还有一个男人也在这里看着
A man was there too, watching.
是他吗
Is it him?
不  是别人
No, somebody else.
这个人头发更浓密
This guy had way more hair.
她什么时候来这里的
When did she come up here?
20分钟前
About 20 minutes ago.
-2603房  -好的  谢谢
- Room 2603. - Great. Thanks.
奥林·泽林可  芝加哥警署
Olene Zelenko. Chicago PD.
不要抓我  是他们让我做的
Please, don't arrest me. They make me do this.
不不不  没关系  我们是来帮你的
No, no, no. It's okay. Hey, we're here to help.
天啊  谢谢你
Thank you. Thank God.
他已经彻底晕了
He's out cold.
他拿走了我们的护照  我们必须按照他说的做
He took our passports. We have to do what he says.
给他拿钱
Bring him money.
知道这个男人是谁吗
Do you know who this man is?
知道  但是我不能说
Yes. But I can't say anything.
他会伤害我的家人  他一直这么说
He will hurt my family. He tells us that all the time.
他叫什么名字  奥林
What's his name, Olene?
告诉我他的名字  我保证他再也不会伤人了
Tell us his name, and he won't hurt another soul, I promise.
尤里
Yuri.
尤里·雷姆诺夫  他是个禽兽
Yuri Remnoff. He's a monster.
告诉我
So tell me.
我给了你们他的名字  现在怎么办
I give you his name, so what happens now?
我只是想回家
I just want to go home.
我们知道  我们会帮助你的
We know, and we're gonna help you.
我们现在必须要离开
We need to leave. Now.
看着我的人叫亚历克斯  他很快就会回来
The man who watches me, Alex, he will be here very soon
-看着我  -好的  我们要找到尤里和
- to check on me. - Okay, we need to find Yuri
其他为他工作的女孩子们
and all the other girls that are working for him too.
但是我们需要你的帮助
But we need your help.
如果你给我一把枪  我会杀了他
If you give me a gun, I will shoot him.
-不不  -我知道你的感受
- No, no. - I know how you feel.
但是这不是我们的意思
But that's not what we meant.
他应该为他对萨莎和对我们所有人
He deserves to die for what he did to Sasha.
所做的事付出代价
To all of us.
我们只想知道他在哪里
We just need to know where he is.
我不知道
I don't know.
只要我们拿到了信用卡的信息
Alex, he takes us to Yuri
亚历克斯就带着我们去找尤里
whenever we get the credit card information.
去哪里
Where's that?
地点信息一直在变
The location changes all the time.
他行踪不定
He keeps moving.
那么你今晚会见尤里吗
So, you'll see Yuri tonight?
会
Yes.
如果你不介意
If you're okay with this,
带上信用卡去见亚历克斯
take the credit cards, meet up with Alex,
一如往常
like everything is normal.
你让我回去再和那些可怕的人在一起吗  不
You want me to go back there with those horrible men? No.
我们会跟着你的
We'll be following you.
我们会形影不离的
We're gonna be there the whole time.
我们不会然你有危险的
We're not gonna let anything happen to you.
我们走  姑娘们
Let's go, ladies.
-不要碰我  -放松  美女
- Don't touch me. - Relax, pretty girl.
我们早点干完  你们早点回家
Quicker we get this done, quicker you're home.
快点
Pospishay.
他们朝前门走去
They're walking towards the front door.
好的  收到
All right, copy.
你的乌克兰语怎么样
How's your Ukrainian?
我只能说一点英语
I can barely speak English.
奥林和其他的女孩呢
What about Olene and the girls?
尤里在哪里
Where's Yuri?
-他不来了  -为什么
- He's not coming. - Why?
他躲着呢  警察在找他
He's hiding. The police are looking for him.
所以他让我来
So he told me to come instead.
回到车里
Back in the car.
看来尤里听到了风声
Sounds like Yuri got the heads-up.
肯定是联邦人员透露的
From the Feds, no doubt.
我们怎么做
What do we do?
所有人听好了
All right, everybody listen up.
撤退
Stand down.
奥林和其他女孩呢
What about Olene and the girls?
让她暂时在里面待着
Keep her in play for now.
警长  她们很害怕
Sarge, they're scared.
盯住那个司机
Just stay with the driver.
你和安东尼奥盯紧  找到他们的位置
You and Antonio hold the main eye, find their location.
除非她有生命危险  否则不要进去  懂吗
But unless she's in danger, we are not moving in, understand?
好的
Yeah, copy that.
你同意这样吗
You good with this?
不
No.
但要想找到尤里  这样是对的
But it's the right move if we want to find Yuri anyway.
-没抓到吗  -是的  他溜了
- So we lost him? - Yeah, he's in the damn wind.
-伯吉斯  来这里  -怎么了
- Burgess, come on in here. - What happened?
我以为尤里在女孩拿到信用卡之后
I thought Yuri was supposed to meet up with the girls
会去见她们
after they got the credit cards.
原因是联邦调查局
What happen is the FBI
-和你的男朋友给我们使绊子  -什么
- and you boyfriend screwed us. - What?
-他们给尤里透露了  -你怎么知道
- They tipped Yuri off. - How do you know that?
我就是知道
Because I know.
我都已经跟你直说了
I have been spelling it out for you,
但是你还是不明白  对吗
but you still don't get it, do you?
联邦调查局的人不关心我们这些小谋杀案
The Feds don't care about our humble little murder case.
他们根本不在意
Not even a little. They never will.
那些所谓的帮我们一把的话
I mean, all that talk about helping us down the road,
都是狗屁  都是空谈
it's crap. It's never gonna happen.
他们会利用尤里帮助他们自己的案子
They're gonna flip Yuri to help their own case.
如果是那样他只会获刑五年
He'll get five years. If that.
对不起  非常抱歉
Look, I'm sorry, okay? I'm really sorry.
我说了  我是想帮忙
Like I said before, I was trying to help us--
我知道  你还是可以帮忙
I know that, I know. And you still can.
实际上  现在
As a matter of fact, right now
你是唯一一个可以力挽狂澜的人
you're the only person who can fix this mess.
但是我想知道
But I need to know.
你是哪一边的
Are you with us or them?
你这边的
I'm with you.
告诉我做什么  我会做的
Just, you tell me what you need me to do, and I'll do it.
聪明
Right answer.
你还好吗
Hey, everything all right?
博伊特昨晚对你大发雷霆
Voight was coming down on you pretty hard last night.
我还好
Yeah, I'm good.
你确定吗
You sure?
是的
Yeah.
金
Kim.
是我  跟我说实话
It's me. Tell me what's going on.
亚当  这个案子要砸了  是我的错
Adam, this is case is falling apart, and it's my fault.
-不是你的错  -是我的错
- That's not true. - It is. It's my fault.
-所以我必须  -干什么
- So now I have to, um... - What?
我必须牺牲我和马特的感情
I have to sell out my relationship with Matt.
我知道这不是你想听到的  但是
I know that this isn't something you want to hear but...
我很喜欢他
I like the guy a lot.
我猜博伊特让你从我们两方之间选择
Let me guess, Voight wants you to pick us or him.
差不多是那样
Yeah. I mean, something like that, yeah.
我们情报组是一家人
This unit, we're family, plain and simple.
但扯上生活  那事情就会有点复杂了
Life gets in the way, makes things a little more complicated.
是
Yeah.
怎么说呢  我觉得有时候
I guess what I'm saying is sometimes
人生就只有错误的选择
you got nothing but bad choices.
无论如何  你都会恨自己
No matter what you do, you're going to hate yourself.
金
Kim.
最起码  你是我认识的最好的人之一
Bottom line is you are one of the best people I've ever known.
所以你做你认为正确的就行
So you do what you think is right.
那就足够了
And that will be good enough.
-好吗  -好
- All right? - Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
什么事
So what's going on?
我都不知道怎么说了
I don't even know how to talk about this.
没事  尽管说
It's okay, just say it.
我老大博伊特  不喜欢跟人合作
My boss, Voight, he doesn't play well with others.
是  我感觉到了
Yeah, I, um--I kind of sensed that.
他觉得你们不会帮他
And he doesn't think that you're going to
找到谋杀嫌疑犯
help us find our murder suspect.
他觉得你们会背叛他
He thinks you're going to flip him,
把他当成反诈骗集团案的联邦合作证人
use him as a cooperating witness in your RICO case.
你到底想说什么
What are you really saying here?
他想让我们开始挨家挨户找人
He wants us to start hitting doors, making arrests.
找谁
Arrests? Like who?
我们一直在监控那些女孩和保镖
We've been surveilling the girls and the bodyguards.
我们拿到了他们的名字和地址
We have their names and addresses.
所以我们想从那开始
And we figured we'd start there,
试试能不能查到上面的人是谁
see if we can figure out who the shot callers are.
好吧  显然这不是
All right, well then, obviously, that's not
那天我们说好的
what we discussed the other day.
我知道  所以我才来找你
I know. That's why I'm here.
谢谢你告诉我
Well, I appreciate you telling me.
我知道你也很难做
I know it couldn't have been easy for you.
是啊  确实
You're right. It wasn't.
不过你做得对  谢谢
Hey, you did the right thing. Thank you.
嗯
Yeah.
今晚见  好吗
I'll see you tonight, yeah?
-嗯  -好
- Yeah. - All right.
伯吉斯很专业  那家伙没有任何怀疑
Burgess is a pro. The guy doesn't have a clue.
好  搞定
All right, bingo.
马特在疯狂打电话
Ol' Matty is dialing up a storm.
我们走运  伙计们
Okay, we got lucky, guys.
追踪到一系列电话
Traced a series of calls.
找到了尤里的藏匿点
Found our boy Yuri's hideout.
他在布里思科4821号
He's holed up at 4821 Briscoe.
那是栋小房子  看来他是一个人在那里
It's a small house, looks like he's there alone.
厄普顿  霍斯特德
Upton, Halstead, stake out
你们盯着那些女孩子在的廉价住所
the flophouse where the girls are being held.
我们一抓住尤里  你们就行动
We get word we got Yuri, move in.
把奥林和其他女孩救出来
Get Olene and the other girls out of there.
-其他人都抓起来  -收到
- Bust everyone else. - Copy that.
好  我们行动
All right, let's vest up.
看来你做出选择了
I see you made your choice.
是  现在我得对此负责
Yeah, now I just got to live with it.
我当着他的面撒谎了  亚当
I lied to his face, Adam.
我把他当猴耍  而且我还...
I played him like a fool, and for good measure, I just...
毁了他职业生涯中最大的案子
blew up the biggest case of his career.
-天啊  我毁了他  -你没有毁了他
- My God, I screwed him. - You didn't screw him.
你只是做出了一个选择
Nah, you made a choice.
你做出了正确的选择
You made the right choice.
嗯
Yeah.
-好吗  -嗯
- Okay? - Yeah.
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD!
你没事吧  金
You all right? Kim?
我没事
Yeah, I'm good.
他跑了
He's on the move!
5021I呼叫总台  有人向警察开枪
5021 Ida Ten One. Shots fired at the police.
疑犯在南边巷子往东逃窜
Offender fleeing eastbound on the south alley.
收到  5021I
Copy that, 5021 Ida.
-没事吧  -我没事  快追
- You good? - I'm good, good. Go!
追
Go.
让开
Move!
Move.
让开  走开
Get out of the way! Move!
-走开  -芝加哥警署
- Move! - Chicago PD!
给我让开
Move, get out of the way.
-让开  -警察
- Move! - Police!
干得漂亮
Nice work.
尤里·雷姆诺夫  你被捕了
Yuri Remnoff. You're under arrest, pal.
漂亮
Good job.
干得漂漂了
That's what I'm talking about.
你们抓了他
So you arrested him?
开什么玩笑  我们不是说好了吗
Are you kidding me? We just had this conversation.
那根本不是说好  布莱恩
Well, it wasn't much of a conversation, Brian.
什么
Excuse me?
我觉得就是你单方面说
Seemed to me more of a speech.
你告诉我你需要什么  为什么需要
You told me what you needed, why you needed it--
你是想跟联调局挑事吗
Are you trying to pick a fight with the FBI?
你疯了吗  你傻吗
Have you lost your damn mind? Are you stupid?
我们有理由相信一个谋杀疑犯
We had reason to believe a murder suspect
要逃出国家  所以我们就行动了
was gonna flee the country so we moved in.
-很抱歉...  -抱歉
- I'm sorry that- - You're sorry?
就这样吗
That's all you got?
你破坏了一项为期两年的调查
You jeopardized a two year investigation
-就因为一个乌克兰妓女  -说话注意点
- over some Ukrainian hooker- - Hey, watch yourself, Brian.
说死人的坏话可不好
It's never a good idea to speak ill of the dead.
她才18岁  被人软禁...
She was 18 years old, being held hostage--
我不在乎她是不是圣人  她就是一个人
I don't care if she was a saint; she is one person.
可是我们在追查的案子
The case that we're chasing...
牵涉到的可是数百...
We're talking hundreds...
数千人的生命
Thousands of lives at stake.
等等
Hold on a second.
你还有什么需要吗  布莱恩
Is there anything else I can do for you, Brian?
喂
Hello?
你确定吗
You sure about this?
确定
I am.
我喜欢你  汉克
I like you, Hank.
但拜托你不要让我来硬的
But please, don't make me play hard ball on this.
你这是威胁我吗
Is that a threat?
别这样  汉克
Oh, come on, Hank.
我们是朋友
You and I are friends.
我绝不会威胁你
I'd never threaten you.
但我现在想兑现你的帮助
But I do intend to cash in on that favor.
-我们说好了的  -我知道
- Now you and me, we had a deal. - I know.
-我愿意兑现  -好
- I intend to honor it. - Good.
但我们不是朋友
But we're not friends.
这件事之后就不是了
Not after this.
这就是犯罪现场的照片
These are the crime scene photos?
我们扯平了
We're even.
我不知道你为什么这么不开心
I'm not sure why you're so upset.
这跟我们之前的交易没什么两样
This is no different than any other deal we've made.
-当然有  -怎么说
- Oh, sure it is. - How's that?
之前的交易
Those other deals...
毁掉的人都是犯罪分子
The people we blew up were criminals.
如果容易  汉克
If it was easy, Hank,
那就不叫帮忙了
it wouldn't be called a favor.
格雷诺议员来电
我能进屋吗
Can I come in?
马特  求你听我解释好吗
Matt, please, just let me explain, okay?